{"data":[{"question":"It was hard not to start laughing when she started to singing.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"hard","b":"laughing","c":"started","d":"singing","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Singing-> to sing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"If you will go to the party with us, I will pick you up.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If","b":"will go","c":"with","d":"will pick","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Will go-> go","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"More people are infecting with HIV this year than they were 5 years ago.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"More","b":"infecting","c":"this","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Are infecting-> are being infected","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I expect you will be surprised to get a letter from my.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"expect","b":"will","c":"to get","d":"my","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n-My->mine","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Last Wednesday I had an accident when I was driving to the work.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had","b":"an","c":"when","d":"the","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- The-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"A child run out in front of my car, and I had to stop such suddenly that the car behind crashed into me.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"out","b":"such","c":"behind","d":"into","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Such-> so","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"It is very bored, and I would be pleased to see you if you had any spare time.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"bored","b":"would","c":"had","d":"any","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Bored-> boring","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"It is pointless to have that old typewriter repair.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"pointless","b":"have","c":"that","d":"repair","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Repair-> repaired","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The sea was so rough that the ferry can't sail.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"was","c":"that","d":"can't","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Can't-> couldn't","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"He lives for the others and he finds his life meaningfully.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"for","b":"others","c":"finds","d":"meaningfully","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Meaningfully-> meaningful","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}